gentsco.com 2018-12-02

# About | Privacy Policy

## This website is provided and managed by Gents, Inc.

Gents recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal and financial information. We have instituted reasonable policies and security measures to protect the information you provide to us. When you register online with Gents and use our online store, you give us your consent to process and use such submitted personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.

This privacy policy applies to all protected personal information collected, maintained or used by Gents.

## What Information Gents Collects

Gents collects personal data from visitors to the website who register their information or who use the online store. We also use cookies (as described below) and track IP addresses so that we can improve our services and enhance your Gents experience.

## How Gents Uses Information You Provide

The data that you choose to provide to us on the website is used by Gents to keep you informed of our special events or promotions, to register you with our website, to administer our website services, and/or to process any orders you may place online. Otherwise, we may use the information you provide to us only to review our performance and to improve our services to you, or to communicate with you about your order if you have placed an online order.

Gents maintains customer data for purposes of customer relationship management, marketing research, analysis and promotion. By giving the appropriate consent on our web siteGents may send you, also by email, announcements on products or promotions and invitations to Gents’s events based on your purchase profile.

If you provide incomplete or inaccurate data, Gents may be unable to inform you of specific promotions or events and to provide you with our services.

Does Gents Share Your Information With Others?

Gents does not sell, rent or, except as described below, disclose our client's names, addresses, email addresses or other personal information to any non-Gents Group entity. Gents may share customer information within Gents Group, so that you may be informed of other products that may be of interest to you.

Gents maintains customer data in our secured electronic Gents Customer Database. In order to maintain our website, to manage our database, to distribute e-mails and to provide client communications, Gents contracts with selected third parties. As necessary, the personal information you provide to us may be processed by these third parties, solely on Gents’s behalf but we do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use of your information.

Gents does not otherwise disclose your information to third parties, unless we are required to do so by law or in connection with a legal claim or proceeding. If Gents is acquired by another entity or is merged or consolidated, information about Gents customers may be made available to the new entity. However, the new entity will agree to protect the confidentiality of your personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy.

## Security

Gents uses appropriate security measures to protect the information you provide to us. However, while we take reasonable steps to protect this personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, you accept that no Internet data transmission can be guaranteed to be secure from access by unintended recipients and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless this breach is due to our negligence.

## Accuracy and Retention

You are entitled to request access to and correction of all personal data you provide us, or to remove your name from the Gents’s marketing list at any time by contacting our customer service department at 866.263.2064 or by contacting us at service@gentsco.com .

## About Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information a web site can send to your computer's browser for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to ascertain which web pages are visited and how often, to make our web site more user friendly, and to give you a better experience when you return to the website. For example, cookies allow us to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you do not have to accept them. To disable cookies, you should access the "help" tab on your browser or read the information that came with your browser software.

However, your visit to our website will be significantly enhanced if cookies are not disabled. If you do not disable your cookies, you accept our collection and storage of any of your personal information such cookies contain.

## Acceptance of Privacy Policy and Modifications

By accessing and using the Gents website (including registering on the website or purchasing items through our website), you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this privacy policy. Gents reserves the right occasionally to make changes to our privacy policy or practices. We will post the updated policy on our website, and thus we encourage you to review this page from time to time, particularly each time you use our online shop.

## Contact Us

If you have any comments or queries regarding our privacy policy or to update, correct or request removal of your personal information from our Customers Database, please write to Gents 6725 W Sunset Blvd, Suite 270, Los Angeles, CA 90028 or e-mail us at: info@gentsco.com
